<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<curriculum>
  <name>Story Hour Academy - Beginning Reading Lessons</name>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL7be6Dn_-FcpFdG7JTfS6Zq17nmdkONce</link>
<publisher>Story Hour Academy</publisher>
  <description>Learn letters and letter sounds, phonograms and phonogram sounds, syllable types, handwriting and related beginning reading skills.</description>
  <grade_levels>
    <grade_level>K</grade_level>
    <grade_level>1</grade_level>
    <grade_level>2</grade_level>
  </grade_levels>
  <tasks>
    <task>
      <title>Single-Sound Consonants - Story Hour Academy - #1</title>
      <description>Collect a pencil, paper, and colorful writing utensils and follow the instructions in the video.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/SH7x8G1bcUM?si=vI7EOP1Iryra0R2u</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter B Video - Story Hour Academy - #2</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter B, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase B's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/V4xEU_B6RJk?si=TIuHzP6Idu3VxJG1</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter D Video - Story Hour Academy - #3</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter D, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase D's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/gOWgs016cyk?si=4iGsjLgsCKlVac8K</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter F Video - Story Hour Academy - #4</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter F, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase F's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/60JdPgGhr3M?si=MG_sx3OV9JbPmy7_</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter H Video - Story Hour Academy - #5</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter H, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase H's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/muP3gQEmeFg?si=QjHS1fU6muzcoO3R</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter J Video - Story Hour Academy - #6</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter J, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase J's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/QNsnJ89eboQ?si=n8ROaA56qRa1X2CB</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter K Video - Story Hour Academy - #7</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter K, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase K's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/qVnR8oOz3IQ?si=rEXWwzjpd7PmtfHS</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter L Video - Story Hour Academy - #8</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter L, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase L's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/14xizMs03nI?si=QWUDp_JVS5Ol6jaX</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter M Video - Story Hour Academy - #9</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter M, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase M's.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/3eYybjnWsOs?si=6u7ImOL2wxXWpayM</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter N Video - Story Hour Academy - #10</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter N, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase N's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/-FGE0BHNfHo?si=9L4H1OlaMHbI87Z4</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter P Video - Story Hour Academy - #11</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter P, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase P's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/yaMGOsTrOi0?si=1mPuJmPoQuB30lwU</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter Q Video - Story Hour Academy - #12</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the phonogram Qu, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the Qu phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/Kt5Nb-Jjlew?si=yEck49s_ICAQGl4h</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter R Video - Story Hour Academy - #13</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter R, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase R's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mDDd9bmO1kc?si=mb9_xzKzqM4kLy4i</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter T Video - Story Hour Academy - #14</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter T, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase T's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/2-V0vZZaiLw?si=Mx9Bt01YZZ7FdZEE</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter V Video - Story Hour Academy - #15</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter V, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase V's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/Y1Qtw7BAmFw?si=ynB-Twh1ecTlO9gy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter W Video - Story Hour Academy - #16</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter W, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase W's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/zrj0P13hvC8?si=RB9b2yGIoQe9Amtb</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Letter Z Video - Story Hour Academy - #17</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter Z, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with the video to write and sound out lowercase and uppercase Z's.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/FbJvRKU74z4?si=-_U0jPXHXeN21eoX</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Review of Single-Sound Consonants - Story Hour Academy - #18</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review the sixteen single-sound consonants in the English alphabet.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/T6W0Td3IOmc?si=wktUOi41_tI9t24z</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z. Ensure mastery before continuing on to video lesson #19.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant Digraphs - Story Hour Academy - #19</title>
      <description>This lesson is an introduction to six consonant digraph phonograms: ck, ch, ng, sh, th, and wh. Follow along with the video to write and sound out these consonant digraph phonograms.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/P5Yk8kX0t9I?si=iqsRbUv0hBGUXtEr</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant Digraph CK Video - Story Hour Academy - #20</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the digraph CK, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the CK consonant digraph phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mtBXKhmSi-w?si=j0FA5hjf6yhExyez</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant Digraph CH Video - Story Hour Academy - #21</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the digraph CH, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the CH consonant digraph phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/DXzuPBySR9I?si=SGsUd-jU9AgdOBA6</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Life of Robert Louis Stevenson for Boys and Girls"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from "The Life of Robert Louis Stevenson for Boys and Girls" by Jacqueline M. Overton.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/lifeofrobertloui00over/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant Digraph NG Video - Story Hour Academy - #22</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the digraph NG, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the NG consonant digraph phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/jznBCqSPTu4?si=UH0kCJQj-58iy6-4</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Robert Louis Stevenson Reader"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "Robert Louis Stevenson Reader" by Catherine T. Bryce with poetry by Robert Louis Stevenson.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/robertlouisstev01stevgoog/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant Digraph SH Video - Story Hour Academy - #23</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the digraph SH, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the SH consonant digraph phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/X4P-Z6gBZmw?si=GG4sZcfpcssv41j-</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant Digraph TH Video - Story Hour Academy - #24</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the digraph TH, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the TH consonant digraph phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/U-q_RP_kN7g?si=26nPkORg9eZ4UKei</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh, th.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant Digraph WH Video - Story Hour Academy - #25</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the digraph WH, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the WH consonant digraph phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/r7zuhy86uXo?si=sJuWYCbJ3HTBYqVn</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Review of Consonant Digraphs - Story Hour Academy - #26</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review six consonant digraph phonograms: ck, ch, ng, sh, th and wh.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/2fWfrUAyIaA?si=JNn7wFdLQy93y3cf</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh, th and wh. Ensure mastery before continuing on to video lesson #27.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Introduction to Multi-Letter Vowel Phonograms - Story Hour Academy - #27</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will get an introduction to vowel letters, vowel sounds, and multi-letter vowel phonograms.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/gXznjEfzQ4w?si=ZTr3HeoxK7b8UQFg</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram AI Video - Story Hour Academy - #28</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram AI, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the AI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/AZp5uIHGkw4?si=O6cJq8A-de2F4ePY</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use page 1 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "A Child's Garden of Verses"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "A Child's Garden of Verses" by Robert Louis Stevenson.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/childsgardenofve00ste/page/n7/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram AY Video - Story Hour Academy - #29</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram AY, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the AY phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/g06u8trY1qA?si=C-5Bq9FvgeoEfrB7</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use page 1 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai and ay.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Under the Window"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "Under the Window" by Kate Greenaway.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/underwindow00gree</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram EIGH Video - Story Hour Academy - #30</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram EIGH, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the EIGH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/8XDvpo1dw2U?si=jWnubTZt1zc0guIC</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use page 1 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, and eigh.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Peter Patter Book"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from "The Peter Patter Book" by Leroy F. Jackson.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/peterpatterbookr00jack/page/5/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram EE Video - Story Hour Academy - #31</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram EE, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the EE phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/RC112BQ9Jxo?si=ERXS-LTFdMtrBG4b</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-2 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh and ee.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Stories for Little Children"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "Stories for Little Children" by Susan S. Harriman.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/storiesforlittle00harr</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram IGH Video - Story Hour Academy - #32</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram IGH, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the IGH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/ILBNaTE8PDI?si=KQuziQbiOvA3b75b</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-2 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee and igh.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Mother Goose's Nursery Rhymes"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "Mother Goose's Nursery Rhymes: A Collection of Alphabets, Rhymes, Tales, and Jingles."</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/mothergoosesnurs00craniala/page/n5/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram OA Video - Story Hour Academy - #33</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram OA, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the OA phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/TEqr45Q3NhQ?si=uzNnF4pSkQwzHLC8</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-2 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh and oa.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Crescent Moon"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book The Crescent Moon" by Rabindranath Tagore.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/crescentmoonchil00tagoiala</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram AU Video - Story Hour Academy - #34</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram AU, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the AU phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/ijuUOLyQKgA?si=RzWyi4UNYapPntbM</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-2 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa and au.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Crescent Moon"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "The Crescent Moon" by Rabindranath Tagore.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/crescentmoonchil00tagoiala</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram AW Video - Story Hour Academy - #35</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram AW, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the AW phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/PcTKYTHDL88?si=b3rhlYC60JG64sg5</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-3 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au and aw.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Little Mother Goose"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "The Little Mother Goose" by Jessie Wilcox Smith.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/littlemothergoos00smit</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram OI Video - Story Hour Academy - #36</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram OI, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the OI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/BddzdtP0J6M?si=0sj7Tb1DdYeEEOaq</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-3 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw and oi.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Little Folks Book of Verse"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read from the book "Little Folks Book of Verse" edited by Clifton Johnson.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/littlefolksbooko00john</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram OY Video - Story Hour Academy - #37</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram OY, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the OY phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/q9Zgwk4C-mk?si=12wOzOFeDAy8_1wN</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-3 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi and oy.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Development"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read the poem "Development" by Robert Browning.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://www.telelib.com/authors/B/BrowningRobert/verse/asolando/development.html</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Story of the Golden Apple"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Story of the Golden Apple" by Pamela McArthur Cole.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://play.google.com/books/reader?id=o1EqAAAAYAAJ&pg=GBS.PP1</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram UI Video - Story Hour Academy - #38</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the vowel phonogram UI, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the UI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/CguDeatwNWQ?si=uVQ6UykLWMQpFqpo</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-3 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, and ui.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Aesop's Fables"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Aesop's Fables" illustrated by Arthur Rackham.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/aesopsfables00chesuoft/aesopsfables00chesuoft_200KB/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram ER Video - Story Hour Academy - #39</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the r-controlled vowel phonogram ER, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the ER phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/8QxDYI_b5fs?si=Ze_55nGZS2y9RP7M</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-4 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui and er.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Gingerbread Man"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Gingerbread Man" from "In the Nursery of My Bookhouse" edited by Olive Beaupré Miller.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/mybookhouseinnur0000unse/page/136/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram IR Video - Story Hour Academy - #40</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the r-controlled vowel phonogram IR, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the IR phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/53E41UMGkQs?si=nfWdHYg0O9H289AY</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-4 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er and ir.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Sparrow"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Sparrow" from "Little Folks' Book of Verse" edited by Clifton Johnson.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/littlefolksbooko00john/page/36/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Fir Tree"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Fir Tree" by Hans Christian Anderson.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/firtreefairybook00john/page/14/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram UR Video - Story Hour Academy - #41</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the r-controlled vowel phonogram UR, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the UR phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/AAgIsJyCdcY?si=stUl4XtnVLVnmv2s</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-4 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir and ur.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Folk-Lore Readers - Book Two"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Folk-Lore Readers - Book Two" by Eulalie Osgood Grover.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/folklorereaders02grovgoog</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram AR Video - Story Hour Academy - #42</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the r-controlled vowel phonogram AR, the sound it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the AR phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/OjLCN-holng?si=VBkvRqgWvdH4uleF</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-4 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur and ar.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Activity - Find the Phonograms</title>
      <description>Look for the following multi-letter vowel phonograms in "The Folk-Lore Readers - Book 2": ai  ay  eigh  ee  igh  oa  au  aw  oi  oy  ui  er  ir  ur</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/folklorereaders02grovgoog</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Arthur Made King"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Arthur Made King" by Emeline Gifford Crommelin.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/famouslegendsada00cromrich/page/30/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Vowel Phonograms OR and WOR Video - Story Hour Academy - #43</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the r-controlled vowel phonograms OR and WOR, the sound each phonogram makes, and how to write these phonograms. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the OR and WOR phonograms.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/Fr4U9hCnQs0?si=7JDv6RuoOFvxDUNn</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-5 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or and wor.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Lullaby Land"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Lullaby Land" by Eugene Field.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/lullabylandsongchild00fielrich</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram EAR Video - Story Hour Academy - #44</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the r-controlled vowel phonogram EAR, the sounds it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the EAR phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/WerFZGbrmWE?si=byRLmXbDGsLDx_Wp</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-5 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor and ear.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Wonder Clock"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Wonder Clock" by Howard Pyle.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/wonderclockorfou00pyle</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Vowel Phonogram OUR Video - Story Hour Academy - #45</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the r-controlled vowel phonogram OUR, the sounds it makes, and how to write it. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the OUR phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/_-450K4utxE?si=RZQxZwS7eZeprmT7</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-5 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear and our.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Fox Without a Tail"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Fox Without a Tail" by Aesop.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/aesopsfables00chesuoft/aesopsfables00chesuoft_200KB/page/68/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Review of Multi-Letter Vowel Phonograms - Story Hour Academy - #46</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review nineteen multi-letter vowel phonograms: ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, ar, or, wor, ear and our.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/8c56tBv84Zg?si=pxvPxyPO16vhXSkg</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh, th, wh, ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, ar, or, wor, our and ear. Ensure mastery before continuing on to video lesson #47.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Introduction to Vowel Letters and the Sounds They Make - Story Hour Academy - #47</title>
      <description>Learn how all vowel letters make more than one vowel sound.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/lCxNfyj2wi4?si=pQvNBZD6ogIA4LO1</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Atlantis, The Lost Island"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Atlantis, The Lost Island" from "Stories from Plato and Other Classic Writers."</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/storiesfromplat00burtgoog/page/n252/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter A Video - Story Hour Academy - #48</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter A and the three sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter A.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mUWbP_lJf_4?si=rB_z-wG2bRSf_XYN</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-6 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, and a.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Raggylug, the Story of a Cottontail Rabbit"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Raggylug, the Story of a Cottontail Rabbit" by Ernest Seton Thompson.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/wildanimalsihave00seto/page/92/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter E Video - Story Hour Academy - #49</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter E and the two sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter E.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/_nMeI_uaGEU?si=0_KTeZOxbB8ffoMP</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-6 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a and e.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Tempest"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Tempest" from the book “Tales From Shakespeare” by Charles and Mary Lamb.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/talesfromshakesp00lamb2</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter I Video - Story Hour Academy - #50</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter I and the four sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter I.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/pdLTB9UQsgc?si=beX1ybMcZGVKg2sG</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-7 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e and i.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "Precocious Piggy"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "Precocious Piggy" from the book "The Riverside Readers, Third Reader" by James H. Van Sickle and Wilhelmina Seegmiller.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/riversidereader00unkngoog/page/n30/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter O Video - Story Hour Academy - #51</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter O and the four sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter O.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/DsbDGKZ1sqo?si=NJ6gD8F1tP37o4ej</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-8 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i and o.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "The Song of the Corn Popper"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "The Song of the Corn Popper" from the book "The Young and Field Literary Readers, Book Two" by Ella Flagg Young and Walter Taylor Field.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/youngandfieldli01fielgoog/page/n112/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter U Video - Story Hour Academy - #52</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter U and the four sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter U.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/761avOJjqGU?si=UQAeCcQGRfI-kR7P</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-8 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o and u.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "Summer"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "Summer" by Elizabeth A. Turner.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/easystories00turngoog/page/n120/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter Y Video - Story Hour Academy - #53</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter Y and the four sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter Y.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/M74XC5S5Yek?si=Y7Ex51uCsChet95f</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-9 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u and y.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "Dumpy, The Pony"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "Dumpy, The Pony" from the book "The Riverside Readers, Second Reader" by James H. Van Sickle and Wilhelmina Seegmiller.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/riversidereader01seeggoog/page/n44/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Review of Vowel Letters and the Sounds They Make - Story Hour Academy - #54</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review the sounds made by the vowel letters (a, e, i, o, u and y) in the English alphabet.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/WCpC1DUcjJw?si=R-IZ4oDNUiswmxfR</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh, th, wh, ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, ar, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u and y. Ensure mastery before continuing on to video lesson #55.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Start a Word Collection</title>
      <description>Print out the word collection printable and get help from an adult to organize and practice new words that you're learning.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/word-collection-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Introduction to Multi-Sound Consonant Letters - Story Hour Academy - #55</title>
      <description>Learn about how the consonant letters c, g, s, and x each make two consonant sounds.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mOjCHQu51-Q?si=BK1rP5M12Op3CxvG</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: A Book of Your Choice</title>
      <description>With help, try reading aloud a book of your choice.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/storiesfromplat00burtgoog/page/n252/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter C Video - Story Hour Academy - #56</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter C and the two sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter C.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/FLVCWF-WXk4?si=g-alkwK6C1K1Ietq</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-10 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u, y and c.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "Belling the Cat"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "Belling the Cat" adapted from Aesop.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/latchkeyofmybook01mill/page/84/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter G Video - Story Hour Academy - #57</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter G and the two sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter G.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/XQ9j1kg9Knk?si=PyfJAI9KE1u5v-cv</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-11 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u, y, c and g.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "The Giraffe and the Palms"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "The Giraffe and the Palms" by M. Genevieve Silvester.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/happyhourstories00silv/page/78/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter S Video - Story Hour Academy - #58</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter S and the two sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter S.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/K1vefUr2UgY?si=K9nP7guVQtiNvaM_</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-12 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u, y, c, g and s.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "At the Sea-Side"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "At the Sea-Side" by Robert Louis Stevenson.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/robertlouisstev01stevgoog/page/n16/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
<task>
      <title>Letter X Video - Story Hour Academy - #59</title>
      <description>This lesson is about the letter X and the two sounds it makes. Follow along with this video to write and sound out the letter X.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/cMbRc0x1XvY?si=HXAzArg7zEzDtghN</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use pages 1-13 of the linked printable to practice the sounds for all single-sound consonants and consonant digraphs. Also, practice all the words spelled with ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u, y, c, g, s, and x.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "The Fox and the Grapes"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "The Fox and the Grapes" adapted from Aesop.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/aesopsfablesinwo00aeso/page/74/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Stories from Greek History"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read about Greek men like Solon and Xerxes from "Stories of Greek Gods, Heroes, and Men" by Caroline H. Harding.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/storiesgreekgod00hardgoog/page/n142/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Review of Alphabet Letters and the Sounds They Make - Story Hour Academy - #60</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review all of the sounds made by each letter in the English alphabet.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/n94EuyRMFIY?si=E2sG_U3pJMEhoF3_</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Memorize the Letter Sounds Song</title>
      <description>Memorize the letter sounds song at the end of lesson 60.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/n94EuyRMFIY?si=d9sVTTMbnFzYlYC-&t=502</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh, th, wh, ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, ar, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u, y, c, g, s, and x. Ensure mastery before continuing on to video lesson #61.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Introduction to Syllables - Story Hour Academy - #61</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn what a syllable is and how to count syllables in words. You will also get an introduction to the six syllable types.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/KkrQf0a-k8s?si=wifb6cxWxDY6hevi</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Closed Syllables Video - Story Hour Academy - #62</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn the definition of a closed syllable and write down some examples of closed syllable words.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mzBXG1dtFUw?si=ieRf3-40yOe9BcWY</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use the closed syllables section on pages 13-14 of the linked printable to practice reading closed syllable words.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n13/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find closed syllable words in Aesop's Fables</title>
      <description>With help, look for closed syllable words in "Aesop's Fables in Words of One Syllable."   Remember, a closed syllable is a unit of pronunciation that includes a single vowel sound made by a single vowel letter that is followed by one or more consonant sounds made by one or more consonant letters.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/aesopsfablesinwo00aeso/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Reading Practice: "Swiss Family Robinson in Words of One Syllable"</title>
      <description>With help, try reading "Swiss Family Robinson in Words of One Syllable" by Mary Godolphin.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/swissfamilyrobinwyssj/page/n11/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Open Syllables Video - Story Hour Academy - #63</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn the definition of an open syllable and write down some examples of open syllable words.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/PphiroQRg0o?si=qi5x92PDjzVOT8eP</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use the closed syllables and open syllables sections on pages 13-14 of the linked printable to practice reading closed and open syllable words.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n13/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find open syllables in poetry</title>
      <description>With help, study the words in "The Children's First Book of Poetry" and find all the open syllables in at least three different poems. Remember, and open syllable is a unit of pronunciation that ends with a single vowel letter and that usually makes a long vowel sound.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/childrensbookofp01bake</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Consonant le Syllables Video - Story Hour Academy - #64</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn the definition of the consonant le syllable, write down some examples of this syllable type, and write some words that contain this syllable type.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/PJHvUreg6ss?si=CEZWyB_TJ2irEFiB</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use the closed syllables, open syllables, and consonant le syllables sections on pages 13-14 of the linked printable to practice reading closed, open, and consonant le syllable words.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n13/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find consonant le syllables in poetry</title>
      <description>With help, study the words in four poems from "Little Rhymes for Little Readers" and find all the consonant le syllables. Remember, the consonant le syllable is a unit of pronunciation that only comes at the end of English words.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/story-hour-academy-poems-from-little-rhymes-for-little-readers</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>R-Controlled Syllables Video - Story Hour Academy - #65</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn the definition of the r-controlled syllable and write some words that contain this type of syllable.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/kiKS68zqtik?si=uBLkxY2YddJOp1if</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use the closed syllables, open syllables, consonant le syllables, and r-controlled syllables sections on pages 13-15 of the linked printable to practice reading words with closed, open, consonant le, and r-controlled syllables.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n13/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find r-controlled syllables in poetry</title>
      <description>With help, study the words in three poems from "Dream Blocks" and find all the r-controlled syllables. Remember, an r-controlled syllable is a unit of pronunciation with an r-controlled vowel sound.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/story-hour-academy-poems-from-dream-blocks</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel-Consonant-E Syllables Video - Story Hour Academy - #66</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn the definition of the vowel-consonant-e syllable, also known as the vce or magic e syllable, and write some words that contain this type of syllable.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/7sJUylknb-U?si=xrVqxC4efTH6nJTQ</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use the closed syllables, open syllables, consonant le syllables, r-controlled syllables, and vowel-consonant-e syllables sections on pages 13-16 of the linked printable to practice reading words with closed, open, consonant le, r-controlled, and vowel-consonant-e syllables.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n13/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find vowel-consonant-e syllables in nature stories</title>
      <description>With help, look for vowel-consonant-e syllables in the book titled "Our Common Friends and Foes: A Nature Reader." Remember, a vowel-consonant-e syllable is a unit of pronunciation that usually ends with a long vowel sound followed by a consonant sound.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/ourcommonfriend00turngoog</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Vowel Team Syllables Video - Story Hour Academy - #67</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn the definition of the vowel team syllable and write some words that contain this type of syllable.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/aCMdwH995iQ?si=nbH662TLWiOMKZef</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Use the closed syllables, open syllables, consonant le syllables, r-controlled syllables, vowel-consonant-e syllables, and vowel team syllables sections on pages 13-17 of the linked printable to practice reading words with closed, open, consonant le, r-controlled, vowel-consonant-e, and vowel team syllables.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n13/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find vowel team syllables in a beginning reader</title>
      <description>With help, look for vowel tean syllables in the book titled "The Child's World First Reader." Remember, a vowel team syllable is a unit of pronunciation with a vowel sound that is spelled with a multi-letter phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/childsworldfirs01withgoog</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Review Lesson of Syllables - Story Hour Academy - #68</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review the definition of a syllable, the six syllable types, and rules for dividing syllables.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/gniRRbSnCec?si=c1flr4kDB3ZKLgeP</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find and study two-syllable words</title>
      <description>With help, use the book "The Velveteen Rabbit" to find ten two-syllable words. Write them down and find the syllable break in each of the ten words. Then, examine each of the twenty resulting syllables and determine the syllable type for each syllable.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/velveteenrabbito1900bian</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>The Schwa Sound - Story Hour Academy - #69</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn about the schwa sound.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/rX7Rtm53WOw?si=DS0DKSp7OdMnYTGH</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Spell a new word with the schwa sound</title>
      <description>With help, find an interesting word in "The American Heritage Children's Dictionary" with the schwa sound in it. Then, memorize how to pronounce and spell the new word.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/americanheritage0000unse_j0b5/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading words with unstressed syllables</title>
      <description>Use page 17 of the linked printable to practice  reading the following words: the, about, dragon, secret, animal, away, problem, offend, idea, custom, system, method and agree.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>More Single-Sound Phonograms - Story Hour Academy - #70</title>
      <description>In this lesson, watch an introduction to 11 more single-sound phonograms: tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, and ti.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/lzCa-kRyUes?si=rOo_LzheNZMmthJ1</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh, th, wh, ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, ar, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u, y, c, g, s, and x. Double check for mastery before continuing on to video lesson #71.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram TCH - Story Hour Academy - #71</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the TCH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/fL6q6XyH-bw?si=U989VcMzzlHu_7t8</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading 22 words with the tch phonogram on page 18 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Assignment: Find the tch phonogram in a poem</title>
      <description>With help, study the words in the poem "The Little Toy Land of the Dutch" and find all instances of the tch phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/latchkeyofmybook01mill/page/334/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Boy Hero of Harlem"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "The Boy Hero of Harlem."</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/latchkeyofmybook02mill/page/184/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram PH - Story Hour Academy - #72</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the PH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/LA4QDt6ajE4?si=BPz2aySnUVNUUqoP</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch and ph phonograms on page 18 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Phaeton"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Phaeton."</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/throughfairyhall00mill_0/page/268/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram RH - Story Hour Academy - #73</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the RH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mhtWqywXj3A?si=LIADRsBbK_s8ASHo</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, and rh phonograms on page 18 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Sunny Rhymes for Happy Children" foreword</title>
      <description>Read the foreword to "Sunny Rhymes for Happy Children" by Olive Beaupré Miller.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/sunnyrhymesforha00mill/page/n9/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Sunny Rhymes for Happy Children" poetry collection</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read poems from "Sunny Rhymes for Happy Children."</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/sunnyrhymesforha00mill/page/n11/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram GH - Story Hour Academy - #74</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the GH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mhtWqywXj3A?si=LIADRsBbK_s8ASHo</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, and gh phonograms on page 18-19 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "A Christmas Carol"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read an abridged version of "A Christmas Carol" by Charles Dickens.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/achristmascarol00dickarch/achristmascarol00dickarch_200KB/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram GN - Story Hour Academy - #75</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the GN phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/y0OgCizkyVs?si=k610BuZnYHKLEWZk</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, and gn phonograms on page 18-19 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Ten at One Stroke"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Ten at One Stroke" by Edgar Dubs Shimer.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/fairystoriesmych00shim/page/126/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram KN - Story Hour Academy - #76</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the KN phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/lLlE50nTWxs?si=pkzpm6T6KMQf61nm</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, and kn phonograms on page 18-19 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "Tales of King Arthur and the Round Table"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read "Tales of King Arthur and the Round Table" adapted from "The Book of Romance" by Andrew Lang.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/in.ernet.dli.2015.12999/page/n1/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram WR - Story Hour Academy - #77</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the WR phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/ihbcXxf7F_o?si=S1Mu6KwDnGqbr9Bj</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, and wr phonograms on page 18-19 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Optional Read Aloud: "The Burgess Animal Book for Children"</title>
      <description>Listen to someone read a chapter from "The Burgess Animal Book for Children" by Thornton W. Burgess.</description>
      <action>Listen</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/cu31924022526457/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram DGE - Story Hour Academy - #78</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the DGE phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/J1wQ64Aj0m8?si=QzqIPH4-Mqy01gf4</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, and dge phonograms on page 18-19 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Rhymes and Jingles"</title>
      <description>With help, read from "Rhymes and Jingles" by Mary Mapes Dodge.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/rhymesandjingle01dodggoog/page/n27/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram AIGH - Story Hour Academy - #79</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the AIGH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/heoWjVkRXhs?si=q_nv0dA1VUMrZqwS</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, and aigh phonograms on page 18-20 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Two Crabs"</title>
      <description>With help, read from "The Two Crabs" adapted from Aesop.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/latchkeyofmybook01mill/page/112/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram CI - Story Hour Academy - #80</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the CI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/ZF5e-rEDvqs?si=rOAfNbyHg77OlHxI</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, and ci phonograms on page 18-20 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Naming the Baby"</title>
      <description>With help, read the poem "Naming the Baby" from "Child's Own Speaker" by E. C. and L. J. Rook.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/childsownspeaker00rook/page/38/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram CI - Story Hour Academy - #80</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the CI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/ZF5e-rEDvqs?si=rOAfNbyHg77OlHxI</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, and ci phonograms on page 18-20 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Naming the Baby"</title>
      <description>With help, read the poem "Naming the Baby" from "Child's Own Speaker" by E. C. and L. J. Rook.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/childsownspeaker00rook/page/38/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram TI - Story Hour Academy - #81</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the TI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/Ye1BsqlMjS4?si=_56s55fEYBeSvgmu</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, and ti phonograms on page 18-20 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "One Thousand Poems for Children"</title>
      <description>With help, read some poems in "One Thousand Poems for Children" edited by Roger Ingpen.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/onethousandpoems00ingprich/page/n7/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Review Lesson - Story Hour Academy - #82</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review the 62 phonograms that you've learned thus far in the Story Hour Academy curriculum.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/OxR93cVoGJ8?si=Zwet2bYkKVfbBKNl</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram Practice</title>
      <description>Use an app or flashcards to practice the following phonogram sounds: b, d, f, h, j, k, l, m, n, p, qu, r, t, v, w, z, ck, ch, ng, sh, th, wh, ai, ay, eigh, ee, igh, oa, au, aw, oi, oy, ui, er, ir, ur, ar, or, wor, ear, our, a, e, i, o, u, y, c, g, s, x, tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, and ti. Double check for mastery before continuing on to video lesson #83.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://www.allaboutlearningpress.com/phonogram-sounds-app/</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>More Multi-Sound Phonograms - Story Hour Academy - #83</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will review 15 multi-sound phonograms and preview 17 multi-sound phonograms.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/20vTsu0Okig?si=fcpsBtYs-OLo-iv0</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram SI - Story Hour Academy - #84</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the SI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/9nn953k_kiY?si=2VuBDJNBVrxUgY6S</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, and si phonograms on page 18-20 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Nutcrackers and the Sugar-Tongs"</title>
      <description>With help, read "The Nutcrackers and the Sugar-Tongs" in "Child-Library Readers Book 4."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/elsonextensionse00elso_2/page/248/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram ED - Story Hour Academy - #85</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the ED phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/IQG1bJwM_c4?si=_bLdhew7HLf66nzn</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, and ed phonograms on page 18-21 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Nonsense Alphabet"</title>
      <description>With help, read "Nonsense Alphabet" in "Verse and Prose for Beginners in Reading."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/verseandprosefo00unkngoog/page/n22/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram ES - Story Hour Academy - #86</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the ES phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/jr079GB6o54?si=gLc8-MAwoBoa2nAO</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, and es phonograms on page 18-21 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Little Birdies"</title>
      <description>With help, read "Little Birdies" in "The Beautiful Book for Little Children."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/beautifulbookfo00shorgoog/page/n73/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram GU - Story Hour Academy - #87</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the GU phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/DOG2LF8-_-Q?si=xDlj0WAsMvuJsVFc</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, and gu phonograms on page 18-22 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Good-Children Street"</title>
      <description>With help, read "Good-Children Street" in "Lullaby Land" by Eugene Field.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/lullabylandsongs00fielrich/page/60/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram OE - Story Hour Academy - #88</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the OE phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/_qtbZQRVEhs?si=h-Av4ipSkSrNlJdy</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, and gu phonograms on page 18-22 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Tiptoes"</title>
      <description>With help, read "The Tiptoes" in "Rhymes of a Child's World."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/rhymesofchildswo00pott/page/22/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram OU - Story Hour Academy - #89</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the OU phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/rb-b4HVNsj0?si=PIsMPeMiBUwp7BiM</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, and ou phonograms on page 18-23 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Wind"</title>
      <description>With help, read "The Wind" by Robert Louis Stevenson in "Happy Hour Stories."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/happyhourstories00silv/page/76/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram OW - Story Hour Academy - #90</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the OW phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/mSqiUK2tnQU?si=-ofcwr3EvFo03jmZ</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, and ow phonograms on page 18-23 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "One Afternoon"</title>
      <description>With help, read "One Afternoon" in "Five Minute Stories."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/fiveminutestorie00rich/page/42/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram OO - Story Hour Academy - #91</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the OO phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/JCVKzAevSv0?si=DlvzydDJ8kz-PLjj</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, and oo phonograms on page 18-24 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Heart of Oak Books - First Book"</title>
      <description>With help, read some selections of your choice from "The Heart of Oak Books - First Book."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/heartoakbooks06nortgoog/page/n20/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonogram EW - Story Hour Academy - #92</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the EW phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/Luqp0Yf8xfM?si=gHjhkGGyntr8LgU_</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, and ew phonograms on page 18-24 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Dove and the Ant"</title>
      <description>With help, read "The Dove and the Ant" from "The Folk-Lore Readers Book Two."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/folklorereaders00webbgoog/page/n24/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Phonograms EU and EUR - Story Hour Academy - #93</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the EU and EUR phonograms.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/E2CSuIh3DHE?si=oPEdcWdglq6JhPpU</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, and eur phonograms on page 18-25 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Little Mother Goose"</title>
      <description>With help, read selections from "The Little Mother Goose."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/littlemothergoos00smit/page/n7/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Little Wreath of Stories and Poems for Children"</title>
      <description>With help, read selections from "The Little Wreath of Stories and Poems for Children."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://www.google.com/books/edition/The_Little_Wreath_of_Stories_and_Poems_f/B57KHYUacTAC?hl=en&gbpv=1&pg=PA5&printsec=frontcover</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Phonogram EA - Story Hour Academy - #94</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the EA phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/GBU6T1d9dUI?si=zFoLlDvINN3qmLLE</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, eur, and ea phonograms on page 18-26 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "As the Goose Flies"</title>
      <description>Read as many pages from "As the Goose Flies" as you can.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/asgooseflies00pyle/page/n9/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Phonogram EAU - Story Hour Academy - #95</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the EAU phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/_rAVOX9CvI8?si=ZV8Nvzrp4i0Pjp70</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, eur, ea, and eau phonograms on page 18-26 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Boy in Trouble About His Old Hat"</title>
      <description>Read "The Boy in Trouble About His Old Hat."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/giftbookofstorie00gilm/page/n125/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Phonogram EI - Story Hour Academy - #96</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the EI phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/TiyRh3SFoFc?si=mK-jlLrcN3bbQJvX</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, eur, ea, eau, and ei phonograms on page 18-26 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "The Boy in Trouble About His Old Hat"</title>
      <description>Read as many poems as you can from "Poems My Children Love Best of All."</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/poemsmychildren00john/page/n7/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Phonogram EY - Story Hour Academy - #97</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the EY phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/fh2lt3Z1wU0?si=EV3bpZaWuaUJjgCK</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, eur, ea, eau, ei, and ey phonograms on page 18-26 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Over in the Meadow"</title>
      <description>Read "Over in the Meadow" by Olive A. Wadsworth.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/latchkeyofmybook01mill/page/64/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Phonogram IE - Story Hour Academy - #98</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the IE phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/BouvL_PN8tE?si=gVX4LW_FJW7fB-MH</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, eur, ea, eau, ei, ey, and ie phonograms on page 18-27 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "Rhymes and Verses - Collected Poems for Young People"</title>
      <description>Read as many poems as you can from "Rhymes and Verses - Collected Poems for Young People" by Walter De La Mare.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/in.ernet.dli.2015.74991/page/n5/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Phonogram AUGH - Story Hour Academy - #99</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the AUGH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/yDVIg66H41I?si=23PyuL3kJGttr6Ax</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, eur, ea, eau, ei, ey, ie, and augh phonograms on page 18-27 of the linked printable.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Reading Practice: "In the Days of Giants"</title>
      <description>Read a chapter from "In the Days of Giants" by Abbie Farwell Brown.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/cu31924012566133/page/n3/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
 <task>
      <title>Phonogram OUGH - Story Hour Academy - #100</title>
      <description>In this lesson, you will learn all about the OUGH phonogram.</description>
      <action>Do</action>
      <url>https://youtu.be/U_KSOyFqfnc?si=_31nF9513QiSloyI</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Practice reading phonograms and words</title>
      <description>Practice reading words with the tch, ph, rh, gh, gn, kn, wr, dge, aigh, ci, ti, si, ed, es, gu, ou, ow, oo, ew, eu, eur, ea, eau, ei, ey, ie, augh, and ough phonograms on page 18-28 of the linked printable. Also, check to make sure you can read all of the words in the "more words" section on pages 29-32.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://archive.org/details/reading-words-and-phonograms-story-hour-academy/page/n17/mode/2up</url>
    </task>
    <task>
      <title>Celebrate with a Visit to the Library</title>
      <description>You have completed all of the Story Hour Academy lessons for beginning readers. Celebrate by checking out a book out from your local library. Try one of the books recommended by Read Aloud Revival on the linked list.</description>
      <action>Read</action>
      <url>https://readaloudrevival.com/booklist/early-readers/</url>
    </task>
     </tasks>
</curriculum>